Guide to the James Lockhart Autry Family Papers, 1832-1998 MS 003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Mississippi, 1840-1875, 148142
  - Jeanie Valliant Autry Brown, 1833-1916; 151685
    - Complimentary ticket to a "Grand Fancy Masked Ball", 1857 Jan. 23; 151716 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Photographs: Jeanie Valliant Autry, 151717 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 4% Registered Bond - Confederate States of America DS, 1864 Aug. 30; 151718 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Jeanie V. Brown calling card, n.d.; 151719 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous Poems typed by James L. Autry for his Mother n.d., 151720 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Valliant and Brahan Families, 1849-1913; 151721
      - Correspondence - Elihu K. Valliant to Martha and Jeanie Valliant ALS, 1849 Oct. 30; 151726 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence - L.B. Valliant to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry ALS, 1868 Nov. 21; 151727 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence - L.B. Valliant to Mrs. Martha V. Brahan ALS, 1869 Mar. 1; 151728 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence - F. and L.B. Valliant to Col. John C. Brahan ALS, 1869 Mar. 23; 151729 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Correspondence - F. and L.B. Valliant to Col. J.C. Brahan ALS, 1869 Oct. 22; 151730 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence - W. [F.] Daniel to L.B. Valliant ALS, 1870 Sept. 27; 151731 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence - W.H. McCardle to Frank Valliant ALS, 1870 Nov. 22; 151732 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence - F. Valliant to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry ALS, 1870 Nov. 25; 151733 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - Correspondence - Frank Valliant to Mrs. J.V. Brown ALS, 1878 Nov. 14; 151734 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - Newsclipping - death of L.B. Valliant, 1913; 151735 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - Photographs - L.B. Valliant, 151736 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Correspondence - M.V. Brahan to James L. Autry ALS, 1873 Nov. 20; 151737 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - Correspondence - Haywood Brahan to James L. Autry ALS, 1880 Dec. 13; 151738 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence - Haywood Brahan to J.C. Hutcheson ALS, 1880 Dec. 13; 151739 (Box 2, Folder 61)
      - Correspondence - G.W. Granberry to Mr. H. Brahan ALS, 1880 Dec. 17; 151740 (Box 2, Folder 62)
      - Correspondence - J.C. Hutcheson to H. Brahan APS, 1880 Dec. 20; 151741 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - Correspondence - Haywood Brahan to James L. Autry ALS, 1881 Mar. 5; 151742 (Box 2, Folder 64)
      - Correspondence - Haywood Brahan to James L. Autry ALS, 1881 Mar. 18; 151743 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Commodore Isaac Newton Brown, 1837-1899; 151723
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence -Chiefly re: Mississippi Plantation [558], 1861-1889; 151744 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence -Chiefly re: Mississippi Plantation [558], 1890-1892; 151745 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence -Chiefly re: Mississippi Plantation [558], 1893-1894; 151746 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence -Chiefly re: Mississippi Plantation [558], 1895-1896; 151747 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence -Chiefly re: Mississippi Plantation [558], 1897-1898; 151748 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence -Chiefly re: Mississippi Plantation [558], 1899; 151749 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence -Chiefly re: Mississippi Plantation [558], 1900-1903; 151750 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence - Isaac Newton Brown memorial, 1916; 151751 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Photographs - Captain Isaac Newton Brown, n.d.; 151752 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Isaac Newton Brown Autobiography (photocopies from Briscoe Center for American History collection), ca. 1885; 167422 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Isaac Newton Brown Autobiography - typescript (photocopies from Briscoe Center for American History collection), n.d.; 167423 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Isaac Newton Brown Autobiography - Miscellany (photocopies from Briscoe Center for American History collection), ca. 1885; 167424 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Eloise Brown Landon, 1876-1912; 151724
      - Landon v. Brown [516], 1906-1907; 151753 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Family Correspondence - Jeanie V. Brown to Eloise Landon, 1902-1903; 151754 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Family Correspondence - Eloise B. Landon to Jeanie V. Brown, 1909; 151755 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Family Correspondence - Received by Jeanie V. Brown after Death of Eloise B. Landon, 1912 Jan.-Mar.; 151756 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Photographs - Eloise Brown Landon's grave, 151757 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Collins Brown, 151725
      - Family Correspondence - Collins Brown to Allie Autry, 1898-1901; 151758 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Family Correspondence - Letters from various correspondents received by Jeanie V. Brown after the death of Collins Brown, 1909; 151759 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Collins Brown [543A], 1893-1909; 151760 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - H.D. Brown, 1914; 151761 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Series IV: Texas, 1875-1998, 148143
  - James Lockhart Autry II, 1859-1920; 148151
    - Sub-Series I: Numbered Files, 1861-1920, 869
      Scope and Contents note
      Not all of James L. Autry's business files are represented in the numbered files. Autry wrote a memorandum describing the function, order and safekeeping of his files. From Memorandum concerning Jas. L. Autry's files (September 7, 1916): All of my files are regarded as personal...the plan of filing is numerical...each file takes a title of subject-matter. Although the various represented companies retained most of the correspondence that dealt strictly with the day to day business, there is still a great deal of important business correspondence and personal material in the files, especially that dealing with his Navarro County Ranch, since he apparently preferred that his secretary keep up such files. The files are arranged numerically indicated by number in brackets after file name (e.g., Hughes Rice Farm [510] 1904).
      Numbered files pertaining to Autry's work for the Texas Company have been removed and organized numerically in the sub-series Business Papers. Also removed are files containing correspondence and records regarding the building of the Autry residence on Courtlandt Place. These have been organized within the sub-series: Personal. Numbered files relating to Autry's legal career have been removed and organized in sub-series: Legal.
      - Memorandum concerning Jas. L. Autry's files, September 7, 1916; 148829 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Autry's Halbert Lots [501], 1887-1907; 1279 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Galbreath Properties [503A], 1909-1910; 1276 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Swayne-Sour Lake Syndicate [504], 1904-1911; 1275 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Dee Carmen Mining Company [504A], 1909-1914; 1274 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Home Place - Corsicana [505], 1904-1910; 1273 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Great Southern Life Insurance Co. [505A], 1910-1914; 1272 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Autry's Ranch - 1904 Matters [506], 1898-1906; 1271 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Motor Boat [507A], 1909; 1270 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - St. Louis Union Trust Co. [508A], 1909; 1269 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Corsicana Cemetery Lot [509A], 1889-1912; 1267 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Hughes Rice Farm [510], 1904; 1266 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Port Arthur Water Company [511], 1903-1913; 1264 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Autry - A.J. Thompson Claim [512], 1904-1912; 1263 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Westmoreland Lots [512A], 1909-1917; 1262 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Natural Gas Syndicate [513A], 1909-1910; 1260 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Autry Ranch [515], 1895; 1904-05; 1257 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Autry Ranch [515A], 1910; 1256 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Southern Trust Co. [516A], 1909-1916; 1254 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Sun-Light Publishing Co. - Reports [518], 1900-1908; 1251 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Sun-Light Publishing Co. - Misc. [519], 1900-1906; 1249 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Oleander Country Club [519A], 1910-1915; 1248 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Morton Survey, Navarro County - Abstract Company Affairs [520], 1889-1906; 1247 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Automobile Club [520A], 1910-1911; 1246 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Moore Farm - Navarro County [521], 1883-1911; 1245 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Magnolia Motor Co. [521A], 1909-1913; 1244 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Houston Lot Offerings [522], 1905-1906; 1243 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Ancestry [523], 1902-1908; 1242 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Sale of Gilbert Survey Lands [523A], 1901-1912; 1241 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Texas Land & Abstract Co. Affairs [524], 1889-1910; 1240 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Texas Land & Abstract Co. Affairs [524], 1911-1916; 1239 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Texas Abstract & Land Company, Incorporated seal, 1238 (Box 33)
      - Minutes, Board of Directors, Texas Abstract & Land Co., 29 Oct 1887 - 29 Oct 1900; 1237 (Box 33)
      - Automobile - Winton [525A], 1909-1911; 1229 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Automobile - Winton [525A], 1912-1919; 1228 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Holly Springs (Miss.) Cemetery [526], 1897-1916; 1227 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Surgical Operation [526A], 1909-1910; 1226 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Autry Ranch [527A], 1909-1911; 1224 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Wilson-Bogy Lots [528], 1901-1911; 1223 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Houston Launch Club [528A], 1909-1914; 1222 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Mexico Fuel Oil Company [529A], 1905-1908; 1220 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Mexico Fuel Oil Company [529], 1909-1910May; 1219 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Mexico Fuel Oil Company [529], 1910June-1911; 1218 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Mexico Fuel Oil Company - Voucher Checkbooks [529A], 1910-1911; 1217 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Mexico Fuel Oil Company [529A], 1912-1916; 1216 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Proposed Sale of Autry Ranch [530A], 1910-1913; 1214 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence - Fred W. Freeman [531] (see also file 523A), 1904-1906; 1213 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - John Thomas Survey - Freestone County [532], 1904-1910; 1211 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Autry Ranch - 1906 Matters [533], 1905-1906; 1209 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Johnson Lots, Corsicana [534], 1901-1908; 1208 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Controversy of Cotton Belt RR in Corsicana [535], 1871-1906; 1207 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Summer Trip [535A], 1911; 1206 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - United Charities [536A], 1907-1914; 1204 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Allen Mining and Milling Co. [537], 1904-1908; 1203 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - James L. Autry School Affairs [537A], 1909-1910; 1202 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Westmoreland Lots [539] (see also file 512A), 1906-1915; 1200 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Sewanee Alumni [539A], 1899-1915; 1199 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Raywood Investments [540A], 1905-1910; 1198 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Raywood Investments [540A], 1910-1918; 1197 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Raywood Investments [540A], 1911; 148830 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Autry Ranch (Micajah Autry Survey) Title papers, etc. [541], 1868-1899; 1196 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Autry Ranch Micajah Autry Survey) Title papers, etc. [541], 1901-1915; 1195 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Texas Laundry Company [541A], 1909-1910; 1194 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Houston Chamber of Commerce [542A], 1911-1916; 1191 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Wortham & Martin (Sun-Light Publishing Co.) [543], 1905-1909; 1190 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Clippings - Various Subjects [544A], 1912-1919; 1187 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Mexican - Gold Mine [545A], 1906; 1186 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - University of Texas [545A], 1911-1915; 1185 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Ranch Affairs - 1907 [546], 1906-1908; 1184 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Mining Laws - Texas Mineral Laws [547A], 1909-1913; 1183 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Drainage District - Port Arthur [548A], 1908-1912; 1182 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Option to Purchase Form [549A], 1909; 1181 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Blackmon-Kerr Co. [550], 1903-1904; 1180 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Oil Leases - Legal Authorities [550A], 1910-1913; 1179 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Autry Ranch - Cattle [551], 1906-1911; 1178 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Freeman Stock Loan [552], 1907-1909; 1177 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - A. C. Hall Account [553A], 1905-1910; 1176 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Political Correspondence [557A], 1912-1916; 1173 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Autry Ranch Matters - 1912 [558A], 1911-1912; 1165 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Corsicana Bonds [560], 1916 Feb 22; 1164 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Houston Hotel Assoc. & Rice Hotel Organization [561A], 1912-1913; 1163 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Freeman's Homestead Notes [564], 1904-1907; 1160 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Union National Bank [565], 1907-1918; 1159 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Autry Ranch Matters for 1913 [566A], 1912-1913; 1157 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Houston Press Club [567A], 1912; 1156 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Barry Investments - Coahoma Trust [569], 1907-1909; 1153 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Committee on Natural Gas for Houston [569A], 1910; 1152 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Sale of Texas Co. Stock to M. Moran [570], 1907-1910; 1151 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Life Insurance - Fidelity Mutual [571], 1895-1910; 1150 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Life Insurance - Provident Savings & Travellers [574], 1888-1905; 1148 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Suburban Houston Property Investments [574A], 1912-1916; 1147 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Magnolia Petroleum Co. [575A], 1913-1915; 1145 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Moving to Houston [577], 1907-1912; 1144 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Margaret Russel Land - Freestone Co. [579], 1890-1899; 1142 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Union Bank and Trust Company [579A], 1905-1907; 1141 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Raywood Corporation Reorganization [580A], 1905; 1140 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Cullinan Purchase of Land from Gipson [581A], 1905; 1139 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Autry Ranch - 1908 Affairs [583], 1908-1909; 1136 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Houston Country Club [585], 1912-1916; 1133 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Fire Insurance [588A], 1913-1915; 1131 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Autry Ranch [591A], 1914; 1127 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Poll Tax Receipts [594A], 1906-1915; 1125 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Autry Ranch Affairs - 1909 [598], 1909-1910; 1118 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Southern Transportation Co. [602], 1914; 1116 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Summer Trip to California & Colorado [608], 1914; 1115 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Business Correspondence - Fidelity Trust Company [612], 1913-1919; 1113 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Investments Offered to Fidelity Trust Co [617], 1914-1920; 1111 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Barry Investments [620], 1914-1916; 1108 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Maps, Geological Surveys [625], 1915-1916; 1107 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Autry's - Asa Chamber's Land [630], 1895-1901; 1105 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Stock Quotations [631], 1914-1916; 1104 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - J.S. Cullinan's New Residence [636], 1910-1914; 1099 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Captain James Garrity [637], 1914-1916; 1098 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Automobile [638], 1914-1920; 1097 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Chauffer's Automobile Report [640], 1914-1920; 1096 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Moore's Bluff Corporations [641], 1914-1915; 1095 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Hogg, Dickson and Hogg [643], 1914-1915; 1094 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Sharp - Hughes Tool Co. [649], 1914-1916; 1092 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Richland Quarry Co. [655], 1912-1919; 1091 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Maturities of Notes Owed Autry [656], 1914-1915; 1090 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Corsicana Cemetery [661], 1906-1915; 1088 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Hawthorne Street Lots [662], 1912-1919; 1087 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Autry Ranch - 1915 [672], 1086 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Chauffeur [673], 1910-1919; 1085 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Eats [681], 1907-1919; 1083 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Raywood Canal & Milling Co. - Elmer Contract [684], 1913-1915; 1082 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Munsey Notes - Navarro County [686], 1913-1916; 1081 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Rufus Hardy Notes - Navarro County [687], 1913-1916; 1080 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Telephone & Telegraph [707], 1916-1920; 1079 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Yacht - Aloha [725], 1915-1916; 1075 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Yacht - Aloha [725], 1916-1920; 1074 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Magnolia Petroleum Co. - Dowling Stock [728], 1915; 1072 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Park Place - Block 32, Lot 9 [731], 1915; 1071 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Freestone Lands [733B], 1918; 1070 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Sharp Homestead [738], 1915; 1069 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Summer Trip [750], 1915 May-July; 1067 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Summer Trip [750], 1915 Aug-Sept; 1066 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - DePelchin Faith Home [754], 1915-1916; 1064 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Emma R. Newsboys Home [755], 1915-1918; 1063 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Louisiana Adventure [756], 1916; 1062 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Hudson Automobile [757], 1915; 1061 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - New York Trip [759], 1915-1916; 1060 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Autry Financial [766], 1916; 1059 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Bryan Barry Investments [769], 1915-1919; 1058 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Eureka Paving Company [771], 1916-1917; 1057 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Texas Economic League [772], 1916; 1056 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - J.R. Sharp Litigations [773], 1916; 1055 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Hot Springs, Arkansas [774], 1916; 1054 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Lucy Waller (Taps) [776], 1916; 1052 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Clippings re. J.S. Cullinan & the Texas Economic League [777], 1916; 1051 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - C.F. Pannill v. Union National Bank [779], 1915-1916; 1049 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Cullinan-Hermann Property [780], 1915-1916; 1048 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Sewanee Debt [781], 1910-1920; 1047 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Cullinan - Smith Street Property [782], 1916; 1046 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Office Quarters - Carter Building [786], 1915-1916; 1043 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Papoose Oil Company [787], 1915-1919; 1042 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Banking & Financial [788], 1916; 1041 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Securities [790], 1916-1919; 1039 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Office Furniture & Fixtures [791], 1914-1916; 1038 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Contributions [792], 1916; 1037 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Office Employees [793], 1916; 1036 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Gross Receipt Tax [794], 1916; 1035 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Campbell - Wren Royalty [798], 1915-1916; 1034 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Pipe Line Tariffs [799], 1916; 1033 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Books & Periodicals [800], 1916; 1032 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Rittman Process for Refining Hydrocarbons [801], 1915-1917; 1031 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Stationary & Supplies - Printed [802], 1916; 1030 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Pettigrew, Oates, et.al. v. Republic [804], 1916; 1028 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Trust Company Charges [805], 1916; 1027 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Estate Inheritance Tax [806], 1916; 1026 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Copper Stocks [807], 1915; 1025 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Autry Ranch [808], 1915-1916; 1024 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Mineral Leases - General [809], 1916; 1023 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Accounting [811], 1916; 1021 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Insurance - Oil Companies [812], 1916; 1020 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Republic Production Co. - Fee Lands [814], 1916; 1019 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Dunlap & Abbott Note [816], 1914-1916; 1017 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - American Petroleum Co.-Pipe Line Dept. [818], 1915-1916; 1015 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Louisiana Leases [819], 1916; 1014 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - East Houston Station [820], 1915; 1013 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Houston Foundation [823], 1916; 1010 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Eureka Paving Co.-Paving Suits & Paving Certificates [826], 1916; 1008 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Santa Anna Farm - Otis Tract [828], 1915-1916; 1006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Florence Crittenden Home [829], 1916; 1005 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Hardy Mining Company [831], 1916; 1004 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Raywood Canal & Mining Company [832], 1915-1920; 1003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Oil Prices [833], 1916; 1002 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Tex-I-Kan Petroleum Co. [834], 1916; 1001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Santa Anna Farm - Artust Tract [836], 1916; 999 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Boy Scouts [837], 1916; 998 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Legal Opinions [838], 1916; 997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence - Office [839], 1916; 996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Legal Department Reports [840], 1916-1918; 995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - East Beaumont Townsite Company [841], 1916; 994 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Law Suits [842], 1916; 993 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - American Petroleum Co.-Railroad Claims [843], 1916; 992 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Trust Funds of Fidelity Trust Co. [844], 1916; 991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - American Petroleum Co.-County Right of Way for Pipelines [845], 1916; 990 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Republic Production Co.-Leases in Chambers Co., Tex. [846], 1916; 989 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Insurance Reports [847], 1916; 988 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - American Republic Corporation [848], 1916-1920; 987 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Delaware Corporation Laws [849], 1915-1916; 986 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Houston Ship Channel Extension [850], 1915-1916; 985 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Rumors and Reports [851], 1916; 984 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - C.W. Miller v. R.O. Eldemire [852], 1916; 983 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - New York Trip [853], 1916; 982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Pennsylvania Tank Car Company [854], 1916; 981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Callaway Foreclosure [855], 1915-1916; 980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Naturalization for Rudolph O. Eldemire [856], 1916; 979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Stock Certificate Registrar & Transfer Agency [857], 1916; 978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Codes [858], 1916; 977 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Petroleum Refining Company [859], 1916-1918; 976 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Bonds-American Petroleum Co. & Republic Production Company [861], 1916; 974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - American Production Co. & Republic Production Co.-Stock Certificate Order [862], 1916; 973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Dr. Frank Crane's "Young Man's Program" [864], 1916; 971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Division of Interest Orders-J.S. Cullinan and Magnolia Petroleum Co. [865], 1916; 970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - American Republic Corporation [866], 1916-1919; 969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Rail Construction-North Side of Houston Ship Channel [867], 1916; 968 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Corporate Calendar [868], 1916; 967 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Pennsylvania Tank Lines [869], 1915-1916; 966 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Vacation Schedule [870], 1916; 965 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Summer Trip [871], 1916; 964 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Employee's Stock Participation Plan - American Republic Corporation [872], 1916-1920; 963 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Wade Ranch [873], 1916; 962 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - The University Club of Houston [874], 1916; 961 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Houston Oil Company [875], 1916-1918; 960 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Prospective Oil Lan-Liberty County [876], 1916; 959 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Shannon Lot, Westmoreland Addition [877], 1916-1921; 958 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Tod Acreage [878], 1916; 957 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Car Equipment Trust Agreement [879], 1916; 956 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - American Petroleum Corporation - Injunction Suit [880], 1916; 955 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - List of Trusts [881], 1916; 954 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - J.J. McClellan for U.S. District Attorney [882], 1916; 953 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Medical affairs [883], 1916-1918; 148831 (Box 20, Folder 2)